[
	{
		"id": "666a588e-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA021",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA022",
		"name": "Bruchsal Fahrtrichtung Karlsruhe",
		"maskFront": "bruchsal-br-heidelberg-fr-karlsruhe",
		"maskBack": "bruchsal-br-karlsruhe-fr-karlsruhe",
		"lastAlternatives": ["3b391188-93c3-4e86-8813-a60bc9f54183"],
		"cameraLat": "49.139238",
		"cameraLon": "8.554712",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "666a5618-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae"
	},
	{
		"id": "666a5366-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA031",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA032",
		"name": "Karlsruhe Nord Fahrtrichtung Basel",
		"maskFront": "kanord-br-heidelberg-fr-basel",
		"maskBack": "kanord-br-basel-fr-basel",
		"lastAlternatives": ["81ddd94e-9fcf-4668-9ea9-36d1485dfd59"],
		"cameraLat": "49.015165",
		"cameraLon": "8.465754",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "666a49e8-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae"
	},
	{
		"id": "666a46dc-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA041",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA042",
		"name": "Karlsruhe Mitte Fahrtrichtung Basel",
		"maskFront": "kamitte-br-heidelberg-fr-basel",
		"maskBack": "kamitte-br-basel-fr-basel",
		"lastAlternatives": ["e5d5fc06-244c-46ea-85b2-a6a320872d4f"],
		"cameraLat": "48.992688",
		"cameraLon": "8.436274",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "666a3cc8-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae"
	},
	{
		"id": "666a39e4-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA061",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA062",
		"name": "Ettlingen Fahrtrichtung Basel",
		"maskFront": "ettlingen-br-heidelberg-fr-basel",
		"maskBack": "ettlingen-br-basel-fr-basel",
		"lastAlternatives": ["f81d8e58-6217-4551-99e5-292c292a24ee", "2bba46c1-0000-46bd-966f-848c178aa601"],
		"cameraLat": "48.960848",
		"cameraLon": "8.408383",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "666a35f2-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae"
	},
	{
		"id": "666a5618-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA022",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA021",
		"name": "Bruchsal Fahrtrichtung Heidelberg",
		"maskFront": "bruchsal-br-karlsruhe-fr-heidelberg",
		"maskBack": "bruchsal-br-heidelberg-fr-heidelberg",
		"lastAlternatives": ["e78f58b2-58fc-4a49-8aed-c6aab16a2cab"],
		"cameraLat": "49.139238",
		"cameraLon": "8.554712",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "666a588e-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae"
	},
	{
		"id": "666a49e8-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA032",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA031",
		"name": "Karlsruhe Nord Fahrtrichtung Heidelberg",
		"maskFront": "kanord-br-basel-fr-heidelberg",
		"maskBack": "kanord-br-heidelberg-fr-heidelberg",
		"lastAlternatives": ["e5d5fc06-244c-46ea-85b2-a6a320872d4f"],
		"cameraLat": "49.015165",
		"cameraLon": "8.465754",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "666a5366-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae"
	},
	{
		"id": "666a3cc8-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA042",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA041",
		"name": "Karlsruhe Mitte Fahrtrichtung Heidelberg",
		"maskFront": "kamitte-br-basel-fr-heidelberg",
		"maskBack": "kamitte-br-heidelberg-fr-heidelberg",
		"lastAlternatives": ["3e11f2d2-1a22-4fc1-ad3b-4066bc685f07", "f81d8e58-6217-4551-99e5-292c292a24ee"],
		"cameraLat": "48.992688",
		"cameraLon": "8.436274",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "666a46dc-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae"
	},
	{
		"id": "666a35f2-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA062",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA061",
		"name": "Ettlingen Fahrtrichtung Heidelberg",
		"maskFront": "ettlingen-br-basel-fr-heidelberg",
		"maskBack": "ettlingen-br-heidelberg-fr-heidelberg",
		"lastAlternatives": ["b3783ebd-3650-4fb2-a769-20528ce554bf"],
		"cameraLat": "48.960848",
		"cameraLon": "8.408383",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "666a39e4-ed7b-11e7-8c3f-9a214cf093ae"
	},
	{
		"id": "a8422667-442a-48ae-9657-5b52a3976c5a",
		"cameraNameFront": "FR042",
		"cameraNameBack": "FR041",
		"name": "Rust Fahrtrichtung Karlsruhe",
		"maskFront": "rust-br-basel-fr-karlsruhe",
		"maskBack": "rust-br-karlsruhe-fr-karlsruhe",
		"lastAlternatives": ["9efd4b83-71ca-4dba-8a5c-7c14117e504d"],
		"cameraLat": "48.251677",
		"cameraLon": "7.761010",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "cc5b0f8c-12f4-4ca4-ae4e-e3cafb02ba03"
	},
	{
		"id": "cc5b0f8c-12f4-4ca4-ae4e-e3cafb02ba03",
		"cameraNameFront": "FR041",
		"cameraNameBack": "FR042",
		"name": "Rust Fahrtrichtung Basel",
		"maskFront": "rust-br-karlsruhe-fr-basel",
		"maskBack": "rust-br-basel-fr-basel",
		"lastAlternatives": ["2003afd7-803c-4fe0-a330-4a4821e04267"],
		"cameraLat": "48.251677",
		"cameraLon": "7.761010",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "a8422667-442a-48ae-9657-5b52a3976c5a"
	},
	{
		"id": "63a26e59-baed-4e5a-b80a-dcb462ffcf96",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA152",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA151",
		"name": "Rastatt Silbergrund Fahrtrichtung Karlsruhe",
		"maskFront": "rastatt-silbergrund-br-basel-fr-karlsruhe",
		"maskBack": "rastatt-silbergrund-br-karlsruhe-fr-karlsruhe",
		"lastAlternatives": ["56e14d1e-0180-411b-b5d2-139d4ae4feb9"],
		"cameraLat": "48.888602",
		"cameraLon": "8.287929",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "d2daa0a9-01b7-4b34-9bd8-86023296837b"
	},
	{
		"id": "d2daa0a9-01b7-4b34-9bd8-86023296837b",
		"cameraNameFront": "KA151",
		"cameraNameBack": "KA152",
		"name": "Rastatt Silbergrund Fahrtrichtung Basel",
		"maskFront": "rastatt-silbergrund-br-karlsruhe-fr-basel",
		"maskBack": "rastatt-silbergrund-br-basel-fr-basel",
		"lastAlternatives": ["b3783ebd-3650-4fb2-a769-20528ce554bf"],
		"cameraLat": "48.888602",
		"cameraLon": "8.287929",
		"street": "70ee0574-289a-4331-90e8-cbfa1c3a798e",
		"sisterId": "63a26e59-baed-4e5a-b80a-dcb462ffcf96"
	}
]
